Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Foreign Politics Serials TAM.765
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Les Cahiers D'Ovtre-Mer: The Overseas Notebooks: Institut de Geographie de la Faculte des Lettres de Bordeaux, Bordeaux, France, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Les Cahiers de la Republique: Andre Schmidt (director), Paris, France, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Les Informations Politiques et Socials: El Centre d'Archives, Paris, France, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Libera!: Libera!, Spilamberto, Italy, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Liberation: Manifest Press, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Libération: Société Nouvelle de Presse et de Communication (SNPC), Paris, France, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Liberté: Lecoin, Paris, France, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 9, Box 38, Folder 19, Box 25, Folder 16)
- Ligne Rouge: Vilmets, Paris, France, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Link: Americans for Middle East Understanding, Inc., New York, NY, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Linke Medien in Kulture: Linke Medien in Kulture, Germany, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Links: Central American Health Rights Network/East Coast, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Lo Magasinet: Landsorganisationen, Copenhagen, Denmark, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- M: Au Bureau, Paris, France, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- M.E.W. Update: Middle East Witness, Santa Cruz, CA, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- M.S.S. Bulletin: People's Mojahedin Organization of Iran, Long Beach, CA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Manitoban: University of Manitoba Students' Union, Manitoba, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- MAPAM: Direct Line from Israel: Department of International Relations, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Marches Coloniaux du Monde: Societe Commerciale d'Affretements & de Commission, Paris, France, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Materialien zum Heissen Herbst gegen die Berufsverbote: Pahl-Rugenstein-Verlag, Koln, Germany, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Memoires de l'Institut Francais d'Afrique Noire: Libraire Larose, Paris, France, 1949-1953 (Box 14, Folder 5-7)
- Middle East Children's Alliance News: Middle East Children's Alliance, Berkeley, CA, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Middle East Coexistence: Young Mapam, London, UK, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Middle East International: Middle East International (Publishers) Ltd., London, UK, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Middle East Labor Bulletin: Labor Committee on the Middle East, San Francisco, CA, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
- Middle East Magazine: IC publications, London, UK, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Mideast Commentary: Palestine Congress of North America, Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Moderne Zeitfragen: Pan-Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Moko: Vanguard Publishing Company Ltd., San Fernando, Trinidad and Tobago, Undated (Box 45)
- Narodnaia Pravda: Redaktsiia Gazety 'Narodnaia Pravda,' Leningrad, USSR, 1992 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 7)
- Nasza Ojczyzna: Warsaw, Poland, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- National Liberation Forum: Movement for a Democratic Philippines, Philippines, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Network News: East Timor Action Network/US, White Plains, NY, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Neue Heimat: German Democratic Republic, Berlin, Germany, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Neue Justiz: Deutscher Zentralverlag, Berlin, Germany, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- New Albania: New Albania, Tirana, Albania, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
- New Bharat: New Bharat Committee, London, UK, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- New Democrat Ontario: New Democrat, Ontario, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- New Hungarian Quarterly: Lapkiado Publishing House, Budapest, Hungary, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1, Box 53, Folder 8-10, Box 54)
- New Party Newsletter: National Committee for the New Party, Ottawa, Ontario, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New Solidarity International Press Service: New Solidarity International Press Service, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- New Statesmen: Cornwall Press, Ltd., London, UK, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- News: GDR-Africa Friendship Society, Berlin, Germany, 1978 (Box Shared Tamiment 051, Folder 16)
- News Bulletin: People's Mojahedin Organization of Iran, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- News from Behind the Iron Curtain: Research and Publication Service, National Committee for a Free Europe, Inc., New York, NY, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- News from Belgium: Belgian Information Center, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
- News From Within: Alternative Information Center, Jerusalem, Israel, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- News of Greece: U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greece, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6, Box 25, Folder 21)
- Newsletter: Brazil Labor Information and Resource Center, Brooklyn, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- NIF Report: New Israel Fund, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Notes et Etudes Documentaires: Secretariat General du Gouvernement, Paris, France, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Nouvelle Gauche: La Nouvelle Gauche, Paris, France, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- NZ Monthly Review: Monthly Review Society, Armagh, Christchurch, New Zealand, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10, Box 53, Folder 6-7)
- Ohe Partisans: F.T.P., France, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Olohek, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Opposition Papers: Agenor / Dialogue for European Alternatives, Brussels, Belgium, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Other Israel: Other Israel, Holon, Israel, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Our Road: Bulgarian Monthly Review: Al. Boneff, Sydney, Australia, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Oxford Pamphlets on Home Affairs: Oxford University Press, London, UK, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- PAIGC Actualites: Commission d'Information et Propagande du Comite Central du Partido Africano da Independencia da Guine e Cabo Verde, Dakar, Senegal, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Palestine Focus: Palestine Solidarity Committee / Palestine Focus, San Francisco, CA, 1983-1992 (Box 38, Folder 8, Folder 16-18)
- Palestine Report: Palestine Congress of North America, Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Palestine Resistance Bulletin: Palestine Resistance Bulletin, Buffalo, NY, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Palestine Solidarity: International Conference of Solidarity with the Palestinian People, Helsinki, Finland, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Palkkatyolainen: Työväen Kirjapaino, Helsinki, Finland, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- PCNA Monthly: Palestine Congress of North America, Washington, DC, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- PFLP Bulletin: International Relations Committee of the Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine, Beirut, Lebanon, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5, Box 38, Folder 14, Box 26, Folder 2)
- Philippine Chronicle: Serafin Ilagan, Chicago, IL, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Philippine Resistance: Third World Documentation Group, Montreal, Quebec, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Polemica: Impreso en Artes Gráficas de Centroamérica, San Jose, Costa Rica, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Political Review: Japan Committee, Nicosia, Cyprus, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Politiek & Cultuur: Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11, Box 54, Folder 2)
- Politik: Aktuelle Informationen der Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands: Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands, Bonn, Germany, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Politique: Politique, Paris, France, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Post-Soviet/East European Report: Liberation Collective, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Prager Presse: Prag Orbis, Hamburg, Germany, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Presence: Cercle des Etudiants, Port-au-Prince, Haiti, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Problems of the People of the USSR: League for Liberation of the People of the USSR, Munich, Germany, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Protokoll der Reichskonferenz: Verlagsgenossenschaft Freiheit EGMBH/Unabhängige Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands, Berlin, Germany, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Re Nudo: Re Nudo, Milan, Italy, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Reconquista: Reconquista, Spain, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Referendum Elections: S.P.T.E.A., France, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Regeneracion: Ricardo Flores Magon, Mexico, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Report of the Tri-Continental Conference: Caribbean October Congress, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Report on El Salvador: Religious Task Force for El Salvador, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Research Bulletin: News and Analysis from the RFE/RL Research Institute: RFE/RL Research Institute/Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, Inc., Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Reseña de Económica y Política: Centro Nacional de Comunicacion Social, A.C., Mexico City, Mexico, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Resistance: Friends of Durruti, Vancouver, Canada, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 26, Folder 4)
- Resistance in the Middle East: Resistance, Cambridge, MA, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Resolutions: Nouveau Parti Democratique Troisieme Congres Federal, Toronto, Ontario, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Revolte: Lutz Schulenburg, Germany, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Revoltes: Yves Dorey, Paris, France, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
- Revolution Democratique Africaine: Parti Democratique di Guinee, Conakry, Guinea, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Revolution: Africa Latin America Asia: Revolution, Lausanne, Switzerland, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Revue de la Presse Francaise: Office of Strategic Services, France, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Saut Al-Thawra: People's Front for the Liberation of Oman & the Arabian Gulf, Aden, Yemen, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Sawt Alitihad: Iraqi Democratic Union, Detroit, MI, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Scandinavian Review: New Sweden, Sweden, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Schwarzer Faden: Reutlingen, Germany, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Science and Freedom: A Bulletin of the Committee on Science and Freedom: Committee on Science and Freedom, Manchester, UK, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Selections from October Review: October Review, Hong Kong, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Senal de libertad/Signal of Freedom: Radio Vencermos, El Salvador, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Simplicissimus: Simplicissimus, Munchen, Germany, 1924; 1934 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Sintesis Informativa: World Peace Council Information Center for the Americas and the Caribbean, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Social Kritik: Selskabet til Fremme af Social Debat, Copenhagen, Denmark, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Solidarity: Czechoslovak Committee for Solidarity with the Nations of Africa and Asia, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Solidarity: Afro-Asian Latin American People's Solidarity Movement (Canada-Quebec), Montreal, Canada, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Solidarity: World Federation of Democratic Youth, Budapest, Hungary, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Sosialidemokraatti: Sosialidemokraatti, Helsinki, Finland, 1958 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 6)
- South and World Affairs: Southern Council on International Relations, Chapel Hill, NC, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Sozial-Report: Inter Nationes, Bonn, Germany, Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Stremlenie: Moskva: Studencheskiĭ Zhurnal, Berlin, Germany, 1923 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Sveriges Riksdag: Sveriges Riksdag, Stockholm, Sweden, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
- SWASIA: Middle East and Europe Working Groups (MEEWG), Division of Overseas Ministries, of the National Council of Churches, New York, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
- The Truth About Soviet Russia: Paper Book Contemporary Publishing, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
- The War and the Working Class: TRUD, Moscow, USSR, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Third World: Editora Terceiro Mundo / Neiva Moreira, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
- Third World Coalition Newsletter: American Friends Service Committee, Baltimore, MD, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Third World Edition: Third World Edition, USA, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Third World Reader Service: Third World Reader Service, Washington, DC, 1975-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Third World Unity: Mukundan C. Menon, New Delhi, India, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Third World Viewpoint: Lloyd D'Aguilar, Brooklyn, NY, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Topical Red Cross News: International Committee of the Red Cross, Geneva, Switzerland, 1965-1969 (Box 54, Folder 8-11)
- Tottenham Community Action: Tottenham Solidarity Group, London, UK, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Trade & Investment: An Activist Manual: International Labour Research and Information Group, Capetown, South Africa, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Transition: Institute for World Order Inc., New York, NY, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Transnational Perspectives: World Association of World Federalists and World Federalist Youth, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1975-1986 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Tribal Notes: Clif Bennett, Hawkestone, Ontario, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Tudeh News: Tudeh Party of Iran, Stockholm, Sweden, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Ukrainian-American: Ukranian News, New York, NY, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 14-17)
- Ukranian News: Ukranian News, Inc., New York, NY, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 4, Box 26, Folder 8-13, Folder 18-20, Box 27, Folder 1-6)
- Ukranian Quarterly: Ukranian Congress Committee of America, Inc., New York, NY, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Update on Guatemala: Committee of Solidarity with the People of Guatemala, Brooklyn, NY, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- USA in Wort und Bild: USA in Wort und Bild, Berlin, Germany, 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- USCFGDR Newsletter: United States Committee for Friendship With the German Democratic Republic, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- USGDR Focus: United States Committee for Friendship With the German Democratic Republic, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- USIA World: United States Information Agency, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Vanguard: Eritrean People's Liberation Front, Rome, Italy, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Viento del Sur: Revista de Ideas, Historia y Politica: Mexico City, Mexico, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Viewpoint: MAPAM/Kibbutz Artzi/Hashomer Hatzair, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Voice of Ethiopia: Ethiopian World Federation, Inc., New York, NY, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Voices for Peace: American-Israel Council for Israeli-Palestinian Peace, Downers Grover, IL, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- WAY Forum: World Assembly of Youth, Brussels, Belgium, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Westminster Review: Leonard Scott & Co., New York, NY, 1850-1858 (Box 20, Folder 4, Folder 13)
- Wir Schuler: Hannover: Arbeitskreis Shuler, Hanover, Germany, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Wirtschaft und Gesellschaft: Vienna, Austria, 1976-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
- Wirtschaft und Statistik: Statistischen Reichsamt, Berlin, Germany, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Woodstock International: Scoop Progressive Media, LLC, Woodstock, NY, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
- Workers Research Unit Bulletin: Workers' Research Unit, Belfast, Northern Ireland, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Working Life in Sweden: Swedish Information Service, Stockholm, Sweden, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- World Affairs Interpreter: Los Angeles University of International Relations, Los Angeles, CA, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- World Affairs Pamphlets: Foreign Policy Association/World Peace Foundation, New York, NY / Boston, MA, Undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
- World Citizen-Federalist Letter: World Federalists, USA & Action for World Community, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- World Federalist: World Association of World Federalists, Ottawa, Ontario, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- World Federalist: World Federalist Association, Washington, DC, 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 10-11, Box 54, Folder 12)
- World Federalist News: World Association of World Federalists, Chicago, IL, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 4, Box 37, Folder 1)
- World Federalist News: World Federalist Movement, New York, NY, 1984-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12, Box 36, Folder 5)
- World Federalist Newsletter: World Federalists Association, Washington, DC, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- World Federalist Newsletter: World Federalists Association, Arlington, VA, 1976-1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- World North-South Issues at the Cancun Conference: Allan F. Matthews, McLean, VA, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- World Observer: Center for International Relations, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- World Policy Journal: Archibald L. Gillies / World Policy Institute, New York, NY, 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
- Young Chartist Daily Briefing: LPYS, London, UK, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Yugoslav Fortnightly: The Association of Journalists, Belgrade, Serbia, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Yugoslav Review: Yugoslave Information Center, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Zprava: Zprava, Uherský Brod, Czech Republic, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 24)